https://www.ccu.edu/privacy-policy/

CCU's Online Privacy PolicyMenu for this sectionSection MenuCCU DifferenceOur LeadershipVisitor InfoFacts and StatsOur Mission Strategic Priorities Statement of Faith Accreditations University President News @ CCUAbout CCU CCU Difference Our Leadership Visitor Info Facts and StatsOur MissionStrategic PrioritiesStatement of FaithAccreditationsUniversity PresidentNews @ CCUCCU's Online Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyColorado Christian University Website Privacy PolicyCommitment to the Protection of Personal PrivacyColorado Christian University (CCU) recognizes the importance of individual privacy and supports an individual's right to control how their personal information is used and shared online. CCU respects the laws governing the collection, storage, transfer, and use of personal data.This policy describes how CCU collects, uses, and shares personal information gathered online through the University's website.Scope of the Privacy PolicyThis policy applies to CCU's use of any and all data collected in relation to use of the CCU website. Please read this privacy policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of the privacy policy is deemed to occur upon your first use of the site. If you do not accept and agree with this privacy policy, you must stop using the site immediately.Personally Identifiable InformationWhen you visit the CCU website, you may voluntarily choose to provide CCU with personally identifiable information which can include direct identifiers, such as name, address, email address, and phone number, or indirect identifiers such as location data or IP address. CCU collects and uses this data to personalize an individual's experience with the website, and to facilitate and enhance the delivery of higher education programs and services.Automatically Collected Data on CCU's WebsiteAs is common practice on most websites, CCU collects certain information automatically on CCU's website. As an individual interacts with the CCU website, CCU may collect information about the individual's visits to the site through cookies and other tracking technologies which store a piece of data on the visitor's hard drive while they are visiting the CCU website. Cookies are only used to identify unique visitors to the CCU website from other visitors during a particular session. A session is the period of active site-use while that unique visitor is linked to our server.Types of data automatically collected include, but are not limited to, search terms used, new or returning user information, browser information, computer or device type, operating system, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and browsing activities on the website. CCU uses automatically collected data to analyze trends, improve user experience, and help ensure information security.Sharing Personal DataCCU will not sell, disseminate, disclose, trade, transfer, share, lease, or rent any personally identifiable information to any third party without your consent, unless it is for purposes of educational service or administrative operations which may include, but is not limited to, providing information to third party vendors, consultants, and other service providers to the University where such information is required or beneficial in the performance of their tasks on behalf of the University. CCU makes no representations or guarantees regarding the policies or business practices of third parties.Data RetentionCCU will not store personal data longer than necessary. How long personal data is retained depends on the type of data and the purpose for which CCU processes it.Payment Card InformationWhen an individual pays for CCU services on the website using a credit or debit card, the information is provided directly by the individual into a PCI/DSS-compliant payment processing service to which the University subscribes. Neither CCU nor its websites process or store credit or debit card information.SecurityCCU is committed to securing personal data. While the University uses security measures to protect against unauthorized access to the personal information of a visitor to the CCU website, it cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication transmitted to or from the CCU website or email through the internet. The University takes reasonable precautions to protect personal information and maintain privacy.ExceptionsOther websites accessed via hyperlinks from CCU's website are not controlled by the University, and are not subject to this privacy policy.ChangesCCU reserves the right to amend this privacy policy at any time, for any reason, without prior notice, other than the posting of the amended Privacy Policy at this website.Contact UsFor additional questions concerning the CCU privacy policy, please email privacypolicy@ccu.edu.Consumer Information + ResourcesConsumer InformationStudent Right-to-KnowTitle IXState Compliance for Online EducationPrivacy Policy
Colorado Christian University uses cookies to enhance your browsing experience through analysis of our site usage, and assists us in our marketing and promotional efforts. By continuing to use the site, you agree to the storage of first- and third-party cookies on your device. Privacy policy.Okay, thanksColorado Christian University uses cookies to enhance your browsing experience through analysis of our site usage, and assists us in our marketing and promotional efforts. By continuing to use the site, you agree to the storage of first- and third-party cookies on your device. Privacy policy.Okay, thanks
